export const javaScriptQuiz = [    {
  question: "Which JavaScript framework has the largest market share according to the 2021 State of JavaScript survey?",
  choices: [
    "React",
    "Angular",
    "Vue.js",
    "Ember.js"
  ],
  answer: "React"
},
  {
    question: "What is the output of console.log('Hello, world!')?",
    choices: ["Hello, world!", "undefined", "null", "NaN"],
    answer: "Hello, world!"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a JavaScript data type?",
    choices: ["string", "number", "boolean", "array"],
    answer: "array"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the result of '5' + 2?",
    choices: ["7", "52", "undefined", "NaN"],
    answer: "52"
  },
  {
    question: "What does the 'typeof' operator return when applied to null?",
    choices: ["null", "undefined", "object", "boolean"],
    answer: "object"
  }
];

export const disneyQuiz = [  {    question: "What is the name of the sword in 'The Sword in the Stone'?",    choices: [      "Excalibur",      "Clarent",      "Caliburn",      "Pridwen"    ],
    answer: "Excalibur"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the giant bird in 'The Rescuers Down Under'?",
    choices: [
      "Orville",
      "Wilbur",
      "Marahute",
      "Aquila"
    ],
    answer: "Marahute"
  },
  {
    question: "In 'The Hunchback of Notre Dame', what is the name of the villainous judge who wants to capture Esmeralda?",
    choices: [
      "Frollo",
      "Ratcliffe",
      "Gaston",
      "Scar"
    ],
    answer: "Frollo"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the villainous queen in 'Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs'?",
    choices: [
      "Grimhilde",
      "Maleficent",
      "Cruella De Vil",
      "The Evil Queen"
    ],
    answer: "Grimhilde"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the dragon in 'Sleeping Beauty'?",
    choices: [
      "Maleficent",
      "Diablo",
      "Smaug",
      "Mushu"
    ],
    answer: "Maleficent"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the castle in 'Beauty and the Beast'?",
    choices: [
      "Cinderella Castle",
      "Windsor Castle",
      "Neuschwanstein Castle",
      "Beast's Castle"
    ],
    answer: "Beast's Castle"
  }
];


export const gotQuiz = [  {    question: "Who is the main character in Game of Thrones?",    choices: ["Jon Snow", "Tyrion", "Daenerys", "Cersei"],
answer: "Jon Snow"
},
{
question: "What is the name of the fictional continent in Game of Thrones?",
choices: ["Essos", "Westeros", "Sothoryos", "Ulthos"],
answer: "Westeros"
},
{
question: "What is the name of the leader of the Night's Watch in Game of Thrones?",
choices: ["Jon Snow", "Samwell Tarly", "Jeor Mormont", "Eddison Tollett"],
answer: "Jeor Mormont"
},
{
question: "Who is the youngest Stark child in Game of Thrones?",
choices: ["Sansa", "Arya", "Bran", "Rickon"],
answer: "Rickon"
},
{
question: "What is the name of the sword that Jon Snow wields in Game of Thrones?",
choices: ["Needle", "Longclaw", "Ice", "Oathkeeper"],
answer: "Longclaw"
}
];

export const javaQuestions = [  {    question: "What keyword is used to define a variable in Java?",    choices: ["var", "let", "const", "None of the above"],
    answer: "None of the above"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the syntax for a for loop in Java?",
    choices: ["for i in range(10)", "for (i = 0; i < 10; i++)", "for (i < 10; i++)", "None of the above"],
    answer: "for (i = 0; i < 10; i++)"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the output of the following code snippet?\nint x = 5;\nSystem.out.println(x++);\nSystem.out.println(++x);",
    choices: ["5 6", "6 6", "5 5", "6 5"],
    answer: "5 6"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the difference between == and equals() method in Java?",
    choices: ["They are the same.", "They compare the values of two objects.", "They compare the memory addresses of two objects.", "None of the above."],
    answer: "They compare the memory addresses of two objects."
  },
  {
    question: "Which keyword is used to define a class in Java?",
    choices: ["class", "interface", "extends", "implements"],
    answer: "class"
  }
];

export const footballQuestions = [  {    question: "Which player won the European Golden Shoe in the 2019-20 season?",    choices: ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Robert Lewandowski", "Ciro Immobile"],
    answer: "Ciro Immobile"
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the 2021 Copa America?",
    choices: ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Chile", "Uruguay"],
    answer: "Argentina"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the all-time top scorer in the UEFA Champions League?",
    choices: ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Raúl González", "Robert Lewandowski"],
    answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo"
  },
  {
    question: "Which coach has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    choices: ["Alex Ferguson", "Carlo Ancelotti", "Zinedine Zidane", "Pep Guardiola"],
    answer: "Zinedine Zidane"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the only player to have scored in a Champions League final, a World Cup final, and a Euro final?",
    choices: ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Andrés Iniesta", "David Villa"],
    answer: "Andrés Iniesta"
  }
];

export const tvShowQuestions = [  {    question: "Which TV show is set in the fictional town of Hawkins, Indiana?",    choices: [      "Breaking Bad",      "Stranger Things",      "The Walking Dead",      "Game of Thrones"    ],
    answer: "Stranger Things"
  },
  {
    question: "Which TV show follows a high school chemistry teacher who turns to cooking methamphetamine to provide for his family?",
    choices: [
      "The Sopranos",
      "Breaking Bad",
      "The Wire",
      "Mad Men"
    ],
    answer: "Breaking Bad"
  },
  {
    question: "Which TV show was created by Tina Fey and is set behind the scenes of a fictional sketch comedy show?",
    choices: [
      "Saturday Night Live",
      "The Office",
      "30 Rock",
      "Parks and Recreation"
    ],
    answer: "30 Rock"
  },
  {
    question: "In the TV show Friends, what is the name of the person that Joey's character plays in the soap opera Days of Our Lives?",
    choices: [
      "Drake Ramoray",
      "Joey Tribbiani Jr.",
      "Joseph Francis",
      "Joseph Ramoray"
    ],
    answer: "Drake Ramoray"
  },
  {
    question: "Which TV show is about a group of survivors living in a post-apocalyptic world filled with zombies?",
    choices: [
      "The 100",
      "The Walking Dead",
      "Lost",
      "Stranger Things"
    ],
    answer: "The Walking Dead"
  }
];

export const friendsQuiz = [  {    question: "What was the name of the original song that Ross wrote for Rachel when they were in high school?",    choices: ["With or Without You", "I Will Always Love You", "Every Breath You Take", "Emotional Knapsack"],
    answer: "Emotional Knapsack"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Joey's agent?",
    choices: ["Estelle", "Amanda", "Janine", "Gloria"],
    answer: "Estelle"
  },
  {
    question: "What did Chandler do for a living before switching to advertising?",
    choices: ["Data Processing", "Statistical Analysis and Reconfiguration", "Transponding", "Procurement"],
    answer: "Statistical Analysis and Reconfiguration"
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the girl who mistakenly believed that Chandler was gay and tried to set him up with her boss?",
    choices: ["Mindy", "Ginger", "Janice", "Jill"],
    answer: "Ginger"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the museum where Ross works as a paleontologist?",
    choices: ["The American Museum of Natural History", "The Smithsonian", "The British Museum", "The Louvre"],
    answer: "The American Museum of Natural History"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the brand of men's lipstick that Joey tries to promote?",
    choices: ["Lip Service", "Manscara", "Joey's Lipstick", "Lipstick for Men"],
    answer: "Manscara"
  }
];







